In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Come out of this body!
All over your body - Holy Ghost fire!
Every part of your body -
Holy Ghost fire, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Why are you doing this to me now? My company will fall.
Every part of your body!
Would you not leave me alone?
Right now,
in the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Go!
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God’s power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV – Changing Lives, Changing Nations and Changing the World.
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 14/07/2018